Okarin?
How?
I can feel her. She's really here.
You're not a spirit?
Do you want me to call the cops?
I just want to know the truth!
You were stabbed right here...
What do you mean by "the truth"?
Are you stupid? Do you want to die?
That's Louise's famous line!
I saw it!
You were stabbed!
Three hours ago,
during Doctor Nakabachi's press conference at Radio Kaikan!
Okarin, try to control your delusions.
Doctor Nakabachi's press conference was canceled!
But...
Ms. Makise! It's almost time!
All right!
Wait! Are you running away?
You're...
I have a name.
It's Hououin...
Kyouma!
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
Time Travel
Paranoia
Are Time Machines Possible?
I'd like to start off by thanking you all for coming here today.
I don't have much experience with lectures like this,
so I hope you'll bear with me.
Makise Kurisu's giving the lecture...
So she isn't a spirit, after all?
Still bringing that up?
I've been asked to speak to you about time machines.
It's a little different from what I talked about in my Science Magazine essay,
but I'd like to give it a try.
Time machines?
I suppose I should just start off by saying that I think time machines are nothing more than a pipe dream.
I'd like to spend this lecture discussing how I arrived at that conclusio—
Objection!
Time machines are an impossibility?
It's far too early to conclude that!
Okarin, you're embarrassing yourself.
You're...
I don't think that timing has anything to do with it.
It's theoretically impossible.
What?
Well then, let's change the format of this lecture to a discussion.
Maybe that will make it a little easier for the more stubborn people to understand.
Right? Mr. Hououin Kyouma?
Makise Kurisu...
And from this,
we can conclude that, in a universe based on string theory,
time travel is completely unrealistic.
Anything else to say?
Mr. Hououin?
I imagine so...
Then why not find some exotic matter for us,
Mr. Hououin?
That's all I have to say. But if you have any further objections, I'm listening.
Mr. Hououin.
Don't be so damned arrogant,
just because you've a little bit of genius!
Wait... She must be an agent of The Organization!
It's hot... It's so hot...
The lecture was, in and of itself,
an act of carefully planned psychological warfare, aimed at me!
Well, I'm not buying it.
Yanagibayashi
Shrine
Eight...
Nine...
Just one more swing.
You can do it!
Ten!
Way to go, Luka!
Okarin!
M-Mr. Okabe... No, Mr. Kyouma.
You forgot the secret words, Lukako.
E-El Psy... Kongre...
Kongroo!
E-Excuse me.
So, what did you want me to carry?
This is it.
Thanks.
Mayushii can't carry all this.
My dad brought them, but there's too much for just us.
I see.
Thank you for donating these provisions to the lab.
This will raise morale amongst the lab mems.
I'm so glad you like them...
Um... Well...
Luka practices swinging a sword daily!
Yes. I promised Oka... I mean, Mr. Kyouma.
When the "Magical Blade Samidare" acknowledges you as a suitable wielder,
it will unleash the hidden power.
Do not forget that.
Yes!
You got such a deal on it at the weapons store... Only 980 yen!
Then, show me the results of your training.
Can you attempt an exorcism?
I-I suppose... But...
If you need a real exorcism, you should talk to my father...
An evil spirit has possessed my right hand!
Hurry and perform the exorcism, before it consumes my entire body!
R-Right!
That's a different hand than last time.
The evil spirit possessed this one today, okay?!
Urushibara Luka.
The mannerisms and voice of a woman...
No... More feminine than any woman.
But he's a guy.
Taller than Mayuri, but so very thin...
Looks great in a shrine maiden outfit...
But he's a guy.
It's already twilight.
Yet it's so hot.
The cicadas are crying.
But...
He's a guy.
Bye-bye!
Luka's so great, being able to do those exorcisms!
He's the scion of a shrine clan.
Sorry.
Restricted
Area
Akihabara
Police
It's off-limits?
Yeah, this leads behind the Radio Kaikan.
Radio Kaikan...
Give me those.
You need to get to work soon, don't you?
Thank you.
I'm working late tonight, so I'll be going straight home afterwards.
Mayuri...
You truly didn't hear a scream, did you?
A scream? When?
Today, at Radio Kaikan.
I don't think I did.
I see...
All right.
That's fine.
Oh, Okarin...
So, nobody remembers...
Not Mayuri.
Not Daru.
Not Makise Kurisu.
Open
Closed
You're closing early today, Mr. Braun!
I told you not to call me that.
I'm interviewing a part-timer today.
A part-timer?
A dreary, declining shop run by
an over-muscled old man needs a part-timer?
You know...
'Sup!
I heard that was the popular way to say "hi" now...
This can't possibly be your part-timer...
Is there a problem?
Your name?
Amane Suzuha.
Age?
Eighteen.
Reason for working here?
I love CRT TVs!
You're hired!
Is this a comedy routine?
Some kind of joke?
Who are you?
His name's Okabe.
He's an oaf who rents a room upstairs.
It's not Okabe! It's Hououin—
Shut it! I'll double your rent.
I'm Okabe Rintaro.
Hi!
Say, what's in those bags?
Special intelligence corn that was donated to the lab.
If you want some, you must appropriately compensate—
Corn?
With the little bumps?
So this is how it looks when it's fresh.
You didn't know?
Can I see—?
Whoa there.
The Organization has targeted many people
for coming into contact with me.
Sara, Claudia, Simone...
I see.
If you want, we could talk about it.
Don't worry about him. He's just spouting crap.
Think what you'd like.
Someday, the entire world will be in the palm of my hand.
So, that's what's popular these days...
Unknown satellite crashes near Akihabara Station, around 12:00...
Crashed around 12:00...
So, Mayuri and Daru were right...
The conference was canceled?
Doctor Nakabachi Press Conference
Makise Kurisu stabbed...
Was that some kind of hallucination?
@channel
John Titor?
A time traveler's here! lololol
SERN has a monopoly on time machines.
No ordinary person, nor nation, nor business can acquire one.
They've only used them for their own self interests,
bringing the world into a dystopia.
I came here to fulfill the noble mission of changing my present.
I came here to destroy the dystopia SERN has built, and once again obtain our freedom.
Then you claim that SERN dictates the future?
You're talking about the so called Grandfather Paradox, huh.
257 Name: Anonymous [sage]
All I can think of is the European Laboratory for Particle Physics.
That's been disproven.
451 Name: Anonymous [sage]
If you time travel, can you meet yourself in the past?
It's possible to meet yourself in the past.
If you do, you simply move worldlines.
What's a worldline?
Inb4 parallel worlds.
Let me begin by saying
that time isn't a single line, moving from the past to the future.
It's comprised of an infinite number of parallel lines, like rivers, called "worldlines."
For example, let's say a serial killer was to murder you today.
If I came from the future and prevented it,
the world would diverge into two lines:
a world in which you had survived
and a world in which you had died.
So, this Titor is Japanese, huh?
A self-proclaimed time traveler,
who appeared on the American Internet, in the year 2000.
He claimed to have come from the year 2036 in order to save the future.
He then became famous on the Internet, and several books were eventually published about him.
But I didn't think I'd see some idiot pretending to be Titor now.
618 Name: Anonymous [sage]
Pretending to be? Huh?
Then let's click this link and read up on Titor!
Daru must've deleted the link on Titor...
John Titor            About 12 Results
Twelve?
Impossible.
Sure, it was ten years ago, but it was huge!
It can't be!
John Titor      About 56 results
They're not here!
They're not here! What is this?
I had a book collection on him, right here.
Damn it!
Hello?
Daru?
What is it?
I'm at Faris'—
What happened to the books?
The books?
The books on John Titor.
I had a bunch of them on the bookshelf, didn't I?
Where'd they all go?
Wait, Okarin?
What?
Who's... John Titor?
I stayed up most of the night looking into John Titor.
I found every bit of information on the Internet that I could.
But...
I want an answer from Titor.
About ten years ago... In other words, the year 2000.
It's interesting that you should ask that.
But unfortunately, I've never been to the year 2000.
Nor do I intend to go there.
Hey! Wait!
You there! You! You!
You took my picture, didn't you?
You should delete it! For your own sake!
I apologize
if I've made you unhappy.
What were you taking pictures of?
Proof.
Of where I walked today... Of what I saw.
I want to ask you about something.
This.
That's a retro PC.
Do you recognize it?
No.
Do you know anyone who might?
Daru, maybe...
Who is that?
He has nothing to do with you.
Delete that photo.
Tell me...
The e-mail...
For that person.
No!
You... Are you threatening me?
If you tell me,
I'll delete it.
Very well.
But I won't sell out my friends!
I'll give you my own e-mail.
What's your name?
It says "Hououin Kyouma" right there!
Hououin Kyouma
Give me that.
Just send me a blank mail.
I'll send something back.
Welcome back, Master!
It's Okarin!
Welcome, Okarin!
Yo, Mayuri.
When I'm working, it's Mayushii NyanNyan!
Come to think of it, "Okarin" kind of sounds like "Welcome."
Where's Daru?
He's in the back.
Kyouma!
I've missed you.
What happened to visiting every three days?
I'm sorry.
The Organization's sabotage has been just awful...
The Organization's gone that far?
Then you'll hold another secret meeting today to decide how to defeat them?
That's right.
Give me the usual Stealth Field.
On it!
I wish you'd let me join in!
No!
The Organization is far too vast for you to handle!
But I've got my forbidden special move...
What?
You finally mastered it?
That's right.
After overcoming months of harsh training in the Highlands of Guiana
and the death of my master, at last I...
I've mastered it!
I'll never forgive you. Ever.
So, about what I said in my mail...
I believe talking to a winner makes me a loser.
Don't worry.
I've no interest in that girl and her lies.
Is this today's "you're the last one I want to hear that from" thread?
Shut up, cheater!
Your 2D wives are crying.
Faris is special!
She may be 3D, but she has a 2D soul!
Anyway, look at this picture.
This is it.
That's an IBN 5100, right?
IBN?
A legendary retro PC.
I think it was about a month ago...
I heard a rumor that there was one somewhere in Akihabara.
She must've heard about it.
What happened?
No one ever found it.
Not even the famous "Lightning Fast Neidhardt" could find it.
Which means it probably never existed in the first place, and that's my final answer.
Is it that valuable?
It was sold over thirty years ago.
At the time, nobody bought PCs. They were too expensive.
That's how stuff ends up incredibly rare.
That girl...
I sent that mail...
I'm Kiryu Moeka...
Sender: The Lightning Masseuse
Subject: I'm waiting
Hououin, I sent that mail! I'm Kiryu Moeka! Age 20! No real job!
I can mail you, right? I'm sending it, whether you like it or not! Moeka
Age 20... No real job...
I'm sending it, whether you like it or not...
Is this the same girl I just talked to?
What's wrong?
Be glad I didn't sell you out.
It's a rare and valuable PC,
but there's a good chance it's not in Akihabara.
El Psy Kongroo.
Master!
Here you go, Nyan Nyan!
The
World's
In Danger ! !
It's my "The World is in Danger" omelet!
Yummy...
Calm down.
The World is in Danger!!
The analysis conducted by the university laboratory
reveals that the gel-banas
have been torn apart at a molecular level.
So they turned into something that was no longer a banana.
That's bad, isn't it?
What's going on?
Right now, the only thing that comes to mind
is the EM-wave effect of the PhoneWave (name subject to change).
What makes you think that?
My intuition as a mad scientist.
So, no reason.
Okay, it's all set.
Then let's use these.
Property of Mayushii
Aren't these Mayushii's?
Don't worry.
I bought them with research funds Mayuri donated to the lab.
Doesn't that make them hers—?
Now, let's toss the whole thing in and see the effect.
Wouldn't just one work? Dumbass.
Can we really uncover the PhoneWave (name subject to change)'s true power
that way?
That (name subject to change) thing is annoying. We should get rid of it.
We can't overhaul the world's ruling structure
if we're stingy with experimental funding!
You're the only one who wants to, you know?
Really?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, done.
What's wrong?
It's gone...
The banana's gone!
Impossible!
It's me.
Execute Emergency Order 666.
Initiate the cool-off!
Government approval?
There's no time for that!
Talking to yourself... weirdo!
Shut up!
Where'd you hide it?
What? You're the one who hid it, Okarin.
I see... I understand!
This must be some kind of teleporter microwave!
Wh-What?
That's insane.
How else do you explain this?
We took the banana from the bunch, put it into the microwave, and...
Gel... bana...
But it's completely connected to the rest of the bunch...
A second ago... We definitely removed one, didn't we?
I think so...
It's really a teleporter?
Is that what it is?
That's an interesting experiment you're conducting there, Okabe Rintaro.
No, Mr. Hououin Kyouma, was it?
Makise Kurisu?
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
ansoku no asu wo negatta
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
habatake butterfly
Spread your wings
kiseki no butterfly
butterfly of miracles
anata he sasagu
I dedicate it to you
namida no butterfly
Oh butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
butterfly of radiance
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
everything will now be rewritten